Ana Chkhaidze: You going?
Ana Chkhaidze: There? You go.
Ana Chkhaidze: But I just, yeah, yeah, okay, I'm not being prompted. I'm just saying what I said, yeah, exactly. Just describe your experience in as much detail as you can.
Ana Chkhaidze: Goodness!
Ana Chkhaidze: So while I was looking at the screen,
Ana Chkhaidze: every now and then, it seemed like
Ana Chkhaidze: like. I didn't know if my eyes were closed like the the color, and like the red and the black kind of blended together, or kind of kind of just became black, and sometimes it quickly became white. One time it it seemed kind of blue, and like suddenly the square kind of like the edges of the light of the computer. Like it. It seemed blue and like it was like rapidly coming towards my vision.
Ana Chkhaidze: For a brief second.
Ana Chkhaidze: Another time. Yeah. It became suddenly seeming white, and I saw a little bit of like little circles, almost.
Ana Chkhaidze: yeah. Sometimes it became all black and kind of blurred, and to the point where I was like, yeah, I thought my eyes. I might have closed my eyes. And I it seemed like they were like on their own kind of closing. I don't know what.
Ana Chkhaidze: why, but yeah, and other times it.
Ana Chkhaidze: It was just just red for a lot of the time. But
Ana Chkhaidze: most of the time the blinking black and red blended together and
Ana Chkhaidze: was just very bright. But I didn't experience too much that
Ana Chkhaidze: things that kind of like showed up differently.
Ana Chkhaidze: Besides, those those few moments of the blue coming towards me, and a little bit of white.
Ana Chkhaidze: Yeah. When things briefly became white. And then after blinking return to normal
Ana Chkhaidze: I didn't find myself blinking a lot
Ana Chkhaidze: kind of instinctively, when at 1st the
Ana Chkhaidze: like, I felt like my eyes were getting uncomfortable or like
Ana Chkhaidze: fatigue. I don't know how to describe it. But when the light didn't look like just flashing anymore, when it kind of became like one
Ana Chkhaidze: one thing in my eyes were like it felt hard to look at it. I found myself instinctively like wanting to blink, and and that kind of reset it, and then I felt I was able to just look at like, see the the outline of the computer again, and the room and the blinking lights. And then the longer I had my eyes open, the more like the outside of the screen.
Ana Chkhaidze: and the rest of the room disappeared. And then the border of the computer the edges of the flashing red kind of just became my whole
Ana Chkhaidze: visual field of like all I saw. Like it. It just kind of zoomed in.
Ana Chkhaidze: Yeah, and and became all I saw.
Ana Chkhaidze: Yeah, I believe that's it.
Ana Chkhaidze: yeah, that's that's about everything I experienced during the time
Ana Chkhaidze: I'm done. I forgot. If you said to do anything, but I didn't want to do the right thing.